- You figured out what you're gonna say?
- You bet.
(Leonard:)I am going to make him apologize for
all the crap he pulled on me in schooI.
(Howard:)That's quite a list.
I can't read your handwriting.
(Howard:)What's that word?
(Leonard:)Scrotum.
(Raj:)What's that one?
(Leonard:)Uh, stapled.
(Jimmy:)Leonard?
- Oh, hi.
- Holy crap, man, it's good to see you.
(Leonard:)Yeah, you too.
(Leonard:)Uh, Jimmy, this is Sheldon, and Raj,
and Howard.
(Leonard:)- Hi.
- Fellows. Can I get a beer?
(Jimmy:)Wow, look at you.
Little Leonard Hofstadter.
(Jimmy:)I hear you're a big-time scientist now.
(Sheldon:)And there's the first zinger. Ouch.
- I'm doing okay, I guess.
Okay?
(Jimmy:)Come on, I read online you're a physicist
at a university. You won some medal.
(Sheldon:)- The Newcomb medal.
- Yeah. Congratulations.
(Sheldon:)Congratulations?
For the Newcomb med?...
(Sheldon:)Oh, please.
That's the scientific equivalent...